(走过的路)
- 你就要死了 Sam - 别说了
- You're dying,Sam - Shut up.
Ezekiel 他是个很好的战士
Ezekiel,he's a good soldier.
我也许可以治好你弟弟
There's a chance that I can fix your brother.
从他身体里面
From the inside.
我相信你 Zeke
I’m trusting you,Zeke.
Metatron骗了我
Metatron tricked me.
他夺走了我的荣光
He took my grace.
我现在是人类了
That’s why I’m human.
不可能再把天使们送回天堂了
There's no putting the angels back in heaven.
天堂被锁上了
Heaven is locked.
混蛋 Cass
Damn it,Cass.
外面正在打仗 是你挑起来的
There's a war on and it's on you.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你不是Ezekiel
And it isn't Ezekiel.
Gadreel
Gadreel.
你想做新天堂的主人
You intended to be the ruler of this new heaven.
我会作为副手加入你
I will join you as second in command.
这是你要除掉的第一个人
Here's the first name on your to-do list.
我叫Abaddon
My name is Abaddon.
我的一贯处理方式就是以暴制暴
War is what I do with my job.
我能给你们找到新的身体
I can get you new bodies.
我将进军地狱
I will march into hell.
所有人类 天使
And all the humans and all the angels.
都将臣服于我
Will bow to me.
天使在互相残杀
Angels are slaughtering one another.
战争已经打响了
It's an open warfare.
没人能逃过一劫
No one will survive this war.
我不得不这么做
I did what I had to.
取回我的荣光
Got my grace back.
不
No.
Oh,no.
Kevin
(如今)
想象大桥坍塌之时
Think in terms of bridges burned.
想象四季更迭之际
Think of seasons that must end.
看潮起又潮落
See the rivers rise and fall.
生生世世永不停歇
They will rise and fall again.
万物皆有终
Everything must have an end.
就像大海终将投向岸边
Like an ocean to a shore.
就像河流必汇聚成川
Like a river to a stream.
当屏幕灯光渐灭
As the light fades from the screen.
终之章节
From the famous final scene.
你还有10分钟上场
You're on in ten.
大屏幕上会打出
The label wants to open with.
Baby Be My Baby
Baby Be My Baby.
接下来你直接唱Baby Cakes
And then you can roll right on into Baby Cakes.
然后就是Baby Maker的完整版
And then a clean version of Baby Makers.
对了 Cory
Oh and Cory,let's.
今天 不要过度调戏粉丝好吗
Try to take it easy with the groupies,tonight.
嗯 随便吧
Yeah,whatever.
怎么回事 保安
What the hell,security.
没事的
It's fine.
Margey你先离开一下
Margey you can go.
什么 Cory
What,Cory.
我说话结巴吗 贱人
Bitch,did I stutter.
你好呀 Gadreel
Hello,Gadreel.
Thaddeus 你换了个新面孔
Thaddeus,it's a new look,I must say.
我还能怎么样呢
What can I say,you know.
被赶出天堂之后
We all got booted out of the penthouse.
总得给自己找个出路
And I just kinda figured.
既然能被他们当成上帝 那我也没必要继续当天使
Why be an angel you can be a god.
你还好吗 老朋友
How are you,old friend.
我不是你的朋友
I'm not your friend.
你这么说就不对了
I think you're being a little bit mean there.
想想咱们一起度过的美好时光吧
Consider all the quality time we spent together.
我被监禁了
I was imprisoned.
而你酷刑折磨我
And you tortured me.
天堂的那些条条框框
Heaven has rules.
你犯了事儿 就得坐牢
Do the crime,do the time,that's it.
我只是犯了个错
I made a mistake.
我只是个小小守卫
I was a guard.
我那么做只是尽职尽责
I was doing my job.
那你对Abner做的那些 也是尽职尽责吗
What you did to Abner,was that your job.
你的男朋友吗 那我只是觉得好玩儿
Your boyfriend...that,that was just fun.
你来这儿就是为了这个吗
Is that what you here for.
来扳回一局
The big pay back.
好吧
Fine.
你想玩儿血腥暴力
You wanna get a little bit bloody.
我也不介意再教训你一次
Yeah,I have no problem kicking your ass again.
毕竟看在以往的交情上
We'll say for old times.
找这个吗
Looking for this.
Gadreel
Gadreel.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Dean
Dean.
Cass
Cass.
看看你 西装革履 卷土重来
Now look at you,all suited up and back in the game.
我不确定
I don't know.
你一召唤我 我就赶过来了
I came as soon as you called,I was.
Dean
Dean.
出什么事了
What happened,what's wrong.
Sammy当时快死了
Sammy was dying.
我还能怎么办
What was I supposed to do.
你让一个天使附身了他
You let an angel possess him.
他说这是唯一的办法 我就相信了他
He said it was the only way and I believed him.
- 现在Sam不在了 Kevin也 - Dean
- Now Sam's gone,Kevin's - Dean.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是啊
Yeah,well.
但抱歉也无济于事 不是吗
Sorry don't pay the bill,does it.
明显也不能让Kevin活过来
Sure as hell it ain't gonna bring Kevin back.
我们一定要找到那个该死的混蛋
We gotta find this son of a bitch.
Dean
Dean.
如果附身Sam的天使不是Ezekiel
If the angel possessing Sam isn't Ezekiel.
那是谁
Then who is it.
死人一个
Dead man walking.
你想杀了他吗
What,you're gonna destroy him.
没错
Damn right.
天使死了 皮囊也活不了
You kill an angel,its vessel dies too.
你以为我不知道吗
Do you think I don't know that.
如果我不亲手结束Sam
If I don't end Sam.
那我就得看着那个天使
And that halo.
活生生把他折磨死 我
Burns him out and I.
天啊 我实在是太蠢了
God I was so damn stupid.
但你的出发点是好的
You were stupid for the right reasons.
是啊 但这又有什么不同吗
Yeah,and that matters.
当然有
It does.
这一点非常重要
Sometimes that's all that matters.
听着
Listen to me.
Sam很坚强
Sam is strong.
如果他知道有个天使在他体内
He knew an angel was possessing him.
他就会反抗的
He could fight.
他能把天使赶出去
He can cast the angel out.
也许吧
Maybe.
但就我所知
But as far as I know.
他现在并不知情
He's in the dark.
我不知道怎么通知他
I don't know how we clue him in.
你还记得Alfie吗
You remember Alfie.
那个孩子 我记得
The kid angel,yeah.
怎么了
Why.
他在临死之前
Before he died.
告诉我
He told me.
恶魔知道怎么钻进他的脑子
The demons were able to dig into his mind.
破解天使密码
Access his coding.
我们也许可以尝试一下
We might be able to do it here.
说不定能绕开天使
Might be able to bypass the angel.
直接跟Sam对上话
And talk directly to Sam.
你觉得这么做会管用
And you think that would work.
我不知道
I don't know.
但我觉得值得一试
But I think we should try.
好吧
Okay.
我们该怎么做
Where do we start.
你们好呀
Hello,boys.
跟你做个交易
Here's the deal.
你告诉我们怎么黑进天使的大脑
You gonna tell us how to hack an angel.
我们就给你注射点儿好东西
And I’m gonna give you some of the good stuff.
人血
Human blood.
新鲜热乎
Fresh from the tab.
听说你对这玩意儿很上瘾
Word is you're jonesing for it.
行行好
Please.
我不需要
I'll pass.
那你想要什么
What do you want then.
首先 全身按摩
Well,for starters,a massage.
戴着镣铐坐着的时间太久了
Between the sitting and the shackles.
身子骨都僵了
The body gets a little stiff.
叫我给你按摩还不如去死
Yeah,I ain't rubbing you.
别这样
God no.
那就去找Kevin
Get Kevin.
他的小拳头做马杀鸡肯定再好不过
His tiny fists can really work wonder.
Kevin死了
Kevin's dead.
哦
Oh.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry to hear that.
别装的好像你有多在意似的
Don't pretend that you care.
别忘了你曾经想要他的命
You tried to kill him.
我早就知道会发生这种事儿
I told him this was gonna happen.
我是唯一警告过他的人
I was the only person who tried to warn him.
我劝他逃跑
I told him to run.
为了提防什么
From what.
你
You.
我要说多少次你才会明白
How many times am I gonna have to say this.
凡是跟你有关的人
People in your general vicinity.
都难逃一死
Don't have much way of a lifespan.
这么说吧
Now.
我不能教你如何撬开一只天使
I can't teach you how to crack open an angel.
这是个充满了艺术美感的技术活儿
It's more...art than science.
但我能亲自动手
But I can do it for you.
至于条件 我只想出去放放风
All I ask in return is a little field trip.
呼吸点儿新鲜空气
Dying for some fresh air.
当然 戴着镣铐
Chains on,naturally.
不行
No.
不行吗
当然不行
Of course no.
如果我是A计划
Because if I'm plan A.
我确定你还有个更完美可行的B计划
I'm sure you have a totally viable much better plan B.
你不能接受他的建议
You can't be considering this.
戴着镣铐他什么也干不了
With the chains on he can't do anything.
那可是Crowley
It's Crowley.
他总有办法做小动作
He can always do something.
看起来这里需要一个第三方
Looks like we need a tie breaker.
把麋鹿叫来 小松鼠
Go get moose,squirrel.
除非
Unless.
当然 他来不了
Unless of course you can't.
这就是你来找我的原因 对不对
That's why you're here,isn't it.
那只巨婴又给自己找麻烦了 是不是
The poor giant baby's in trouble again,isn't he.
你废话完了没有
Are you done.
看情况
Depends.
这么说我们达成协议了
Do we have a deal.
是的
Yeah.
好极了 什么时候出发
Excellent,when do we leave.
等我想办法搞到辆车
As soon as I can scrounge up a ride.
我有车
I have a vehicle.
不知道为什么 在几公里外停下不走了
It stopped a few miles from here,inexplicably.
开什么玩笑
Really.
你怎么回事 去拉皮条了
What are you?A pimp.
我还挺喜欢
I've liked it.
只是没油了
Yeah,it's out of gas.
让我猜猜 神奇小子
Riddle me this,boy wonder.
为什么你会需要一辆车
Why do you need the wheels.
如果你背叛我们
When you betray us.
我就把你的心活活挖出来
I’ll be the one to carve out your heart.
哦 Cass 你可真会调情
Oh,Cass.Such a flirt.
好了
All right.
走吧
Let's go.
我坐副驾座吗
Shotgun.
不行
Wrong.
你坐后面
You're in the back.
你也是 好好盯着他
Hey,you too,keep an eye on him.
嘿 别挤着我的腿
Hey,watch the leg.
你就坐我旁边
You're on my side.
你们够了
Hey,hey,hey.
还需要什么吗
Get you need anything else.
不用了 谢谢
I'm good,thanks.
欢迎回来 小甜心
Welcome home,sweethearts.
看到一幅这么老的皮囊很不习惯吧
Strange seeing an old vessel,isn't it.
就好像在看一面哈哈镜
Like looking into a funhouse mirror.
先谈正事儿
But first things first.
我给你的任务 有遇到什么麻烦吗
The tasks I gave you,any hiccups.
杀Thaddeus并不难
Killing Thaddeus was easy.
他死有余辜
He had it coming.
我知道你过去的事儿
I know all about your history.
不然我为什么给你他的名字
Why do you think I give you his name.
就当是你的入伙奖金好了
Considering it your signing bonus.
那个孩子呢
And the kid.
确实
That was.
不容易
Less easy.
他曾是个威胁
He was a threat.
但我改主意了
But I flipped the switch upstairs.
现在 Kevin不在了
And now that Kevin is gone and.
就再也没有先知了
There will be no more prophets.
Dean Winchester呢
What about Dean Winchester.
你从来没给过我他的名字 Metatron
You never give me his name,Metatron.
看来你还不懂得主动
Now much for seizing initiatives,are we.
Gadreel 我们在创写我们自己的传奇
Gadreel,we're writing our own epic story here.
要让这一切顺利进行 有时候
To make that work,sometimes.
你必须杀了你最爱的人
You have to kill your darlings.
又不是说你以前没干过更糟的
It's not like you haven't done worse before.
抱歉
Sorry,sorry.
新任务
Onto new business.
你的下一个目标
Your next target.
我还需要取走多少性命
How many more lives do I have to take.
你的职责
It's not your place.
不是问问题
To ask questions.
而是服从命令
It is your place to obey.
你想成为我的副手
You wanna be my second in command.
那就证明你准备好了
Prove you are ready.
证明你的忠诚
Prove you are loyal.
或者什么都不做
Or don't.
退出
Walk away.
你就又是 叛变的Gadreel
Go back to be Gadreel the traitor.
可悲的倒霉蛋
The sap.
天堂里经久不衰的笑话
Heaven's longest running joke.
Abaddon
Abaddon.
我找到他了
I found him.
Crowley出来活动了
Crowley is on the move.
你的线人在这儿吗
Your source is in here.
她能查到任何你需要的信息
And she can track anything you need.
甚至是咱们跑丢的Samantha
Even our little lost Samantha.
怎么会
How.
这个地方 不是看起来的那么简单
Well,this place isn't really THIS.
这是国家安全局监听部的伪装
It's a front for NSA listening post.
- 他们在监听什么 - 所有事
- What are they listening for - Everything.
美国政府近些年来有点儿偷窥狂的倾向
The US government is quite the voyeur these days.
所以我安插了一个最好的手下 让她在里面工作
So I planted one of my best,and let it go to work.
寻找恐怖分子吗
Looking for terrorists.
寻找一切迹象 笨蛋
Looking for marks,slow boat.
Crowley先生
Mr.Crowley.
她现在可以见你了
She'll see you now.
只见Crowley先生
Just...Mr.Crowley.
我会听着你说的每一个字
I'll be listening to every word you say.
保证哦
Promise.
Cecily 别来无恙
Cecily,how are you.
倒是比你好很多
Better than you.
跟你来的是Dean Winchester和 Castiel
That was Dean Winchester and...Castiel.
我懂 没有领带的小天使
Yes,I know,without the...tie.
- 确实不太好认 很 - 火辣
- It's barely recognizable,so - Hot.
我的意思是 人形Castiel不是我的菜
I mean,human Castiel?Nah.
但是天使Castiel 性感极了
But feathered Castiel,Phew.
什么人形Castiel
Human Castiel.
你知道他之前经历了什么 对吧
You heard what happened to him,right.
我被绑起来了
I've been tied up.
有什么尽管说吧
Pray,do tell.
听到什么了吗
Hear anything.
没有
No.
Crowley进的房间被屏蔽了
Room Crowley's been in has been warded.
真棒 真是
Awesome,that's.
太棒了
Freaking awesome.
也就是说性感小队长 把另一个天使
So Captain Sexy out there,totally cuts another.
的喉咙割开 取走了他的荣光 现在
Angel's throat,yoinks his grace,and now.
他又是天使了
He's got his mojo back.
但翅膀仍没有复原
Minus the broken wings.
我知道他为什么会需要一辆车了
Well that explains the hooptie.
我是说这一切
I mean,all this.
你怎么知道的
How.
我对一颗卫星做了点儿手脚 让它接收天使电台
I tuned up one of our satellites to pick angel radio.
真厉害
Impressive.
是啊 我可不光是脸蛋漂亮
Yeah,not just a pretty face.
地狱那边怎么样了
What about Hell.
呃 根本就没有人坚守自己的工作
Ugh,no one's doing their job.
我每周都往地狱传很多口讯 但是
I send oodles of data down there every week,but.
地狱在乎吗 答案是不
Does hell give a damn?No.
当然 在Abaddon的领导下 你
Of course,with Abaddon in charge you.
我可不承认那个婊子是我老大
Oh,that B with an Itch ain't the boss.
我的意思是 她也只是
I mean she's got a few more.
赢得了几个激进分子
Aggro types on her side.
但是大多数人还是等着你回去
But most just waiting to see you take the belt.
不是你就是她
You or her.
他们还怕我
They're still afraid of me.
估计是因为他们还不知道你被铐住了
Probably cause they don't know you're in cuffs.
说到这个
Speaking of which.
有办法吗
Do they come off.
没有钥匙就不行
Not without the key.
好吧
Fine.
帮我个忙
Need you to do me a favor.
能帮我找一下这辆车吗
Can you find this car for me.
小菜一碟
Easy-peasy.
很高兴知道有人依旧忠诚
Nice to know someone's still loyal.
是啊
Uh Huh.
当然 是在你没有两边都讨好的前提下
That is,of course,you're not playing both sides.
你会吗
Wouldn't you.
你那个开走车的小伙伴 10分钟前
Your fellows on wheels just run a red light.
在宾州的萨摩赛特刚闯了红灯
In Somerset Pennsylvania 10 minutes ago.
走吧
Let's go.
三个好闺蜜又要相聚了
The three amigos ride again.
他不是我闺蜜
He's not my amigo.
- Alexandra Sarver吗 - 是
- Alexandra Sarver - Yeah.
- Gadreel - Abner
- Gadreel - Abner.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
出什么事儿了
What happened.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here.
我 你在这儿干什么
I...what are you doing here.
爸爸 爸爸
Daddy,daddy.
Delilah 这是爸爸最好的朋友
Delilah,this is daddy's best friend.
可以打个招呼吗
Can you say hi.
嗨
Hi.
你有孩子了
You have a child.
我有家 Gadreel
I have family,Gadreel.
我妻子待会儿要带她去看电影
Look,my wife and the niblet are going to movie.
几个小时后回来 我们可以好好聊聊
Swing back in a few hours so we can catch up,okay.
好 行
Okay,sure.
这么说 你有了份工作
So,you have a job.
售后服务
Customer support.
主要都是电脑问题
Computers,mostly.
就跟回应祈祷差不多 不过
It's like answering prayers,but.
是付钱的
They pay for it.
- 你变了 Abner - 是啊
- You have changed,Abner - Yeah.
我不是个称职的天使
Well,I was a crappy angel.
喜怒无常
I was petulant.
我罪有应得
And I deserted my post.
我在天堂被关了700年
I spend 7 hundred years in heaven's lockup,I.
算了 都过去了
No,doesn't matter.
我们现在跟Thaddeus再无瓜葛了
We're long way from Thaddeus now.
我杀了他 Abner
I killed him,Abner.
帮我们报了仇
I got our revenge.
我倒希望你没那么做
Wish you hadn't done that.
为什么
Why.
他折磨我们 折磨你最多
He tortured us,you most of all.
我记得
I remember.
我还记得你总是在我身边
And I remember you were always there.
帮我疗伤
To put me back together.
- 那时我们是朋友 - 现在我们也是朋友
- We were friends - We are friends.
这次坠天 是我们的新开始
And the fall,it’s our second chance.
忘了我们的仇恨 忘了我们是谁
You can forget all our hates,who we were.
说得容易
It's not that easy.
确实很容易
Yes,it is.
看看我
Look at me.
我很幸福
I'm happy.
你的容器 他幸福吗
And your vessel,is he happy.
他只是个有施虐倾向的混蛋
He was an abusive ass.
我爱我的家人
I love my family.
他们也爱我
And they love me.
我一点儿都不聪明 Gadreel
I'm not a wise man,Gadreel.
但是我知道 幸福的秘诀
But I know this,the key to happiness.
是努力得到你最想要的
It's getting the one thing you want most.
之后再也不放手
And never letting it go.
那代价呢
And what if there's a price.
凡事都有代价
There's always...a price.
但那都是值得的
But it's worth paying.
你不该来这里的 Dean
You should not have come here,Dean.
你杀了我的朋友
You killed my friend.
挟持了我弟弟
And you take my brother.
你觉得我会放过你吗
And you think I'm gonna let that stand.
我让你活了下来
I allowed you to live.
你的疏忽
Mistake.
所以 Crowley来过
So Crowley was here.
是的 我觉得你应该想知道
Yeah,I thought you'd want to know.
你想的没错
You thought right.
现在 知道他跑去哪里了吗
And now,any idea where he scampered off to.
宾州的萨摩赛特
Somerset Pennsylvania.
和Dean Winchester还有Castiel一起
With Dean Winchester and the angel Castiel.
你怎么知道的
And you know this how.
他们在找一辆Impala车
They are chasing an Impala.
我帮他们找到了
I helped them track it.
你帮助了Crowley吗
You,helped Crowley.
是的 我要伺机而动 直到其中一方
Yeah,I'm kinda playing both sides until someone.
直到你赢了为止
Until you win.
挺明智的 对吧
Smart,right.
不
No.
恰恰相反
Sort of the opposite.
欢迎来参加派对 伙计
Welcome to the party,pal.
Cass 现在什么情况
Cass,how are we looking.
Sam大多数的内伤都恢复了
Most of Sam's internal burns have healed.
我可以帮他治好剩下的
I should be able to fix the rest.
你叫什么
What's your name.
我以为我认识天堂里每一个天使
I thought I knew every angel in heaven.
但我从来没见过你
But I've never seen you.
为什么我要回答你的问题
Why would I tell you anything.
我不在乎你是谁
I don't give a damn who you are.
你马上给我滚出去
You need to get out.
现在就滚
Now.
如果我不走呢
And if I don't.
那么你就要和我愉快地玩耍一阵子了
And you and I will have a lovely little play date.
就算被绑住了 我还是能把这个肉身撕碎
Even bound,I can rip this body apart.
告诉他们 Castiel
Tell them,Castiel.
这么做了你就死定了
You do you die.
你想一切都结束吗
You want this to end.
动手吧
Go ahead.
在你弟弟的心脏上捅一刀
Put a blade through your brother's heart.
说点让你宽心的
If it makes you feel better.
我把Sam锁在一个梦境里了
I have Sam locked away in a dream.
所以他现在以为
As far as he knows.
你们两个正在查一个案子
Two of you are working a case right now.
有食尸鬼和拉拉队长什么的
Something with ghouls and cheerleaders.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this.
我们曾经并肩作战
We fought together.
我那么相信你
And I trusted you.
我以为你是正义的一方
I thought you were one of the good guys.
我只是在做我必须做的
I am doing what I have to do.
我也是
So am I.
还有我
我看不下去了
I can't watch it anymore.
我懂
I understand.
虽然折磨的不是Sam 但又还是他
It's not Sam,but,still Sam.
差不多就是这个感觉 对
Pretty much,yeah.
你怎么样了
How are you doing.
什么 你在这个时候想到关心我
What,you want to talk about me now.
我想谈谈除了有个恶魔正在用针
I want to talk about anything.
扎进我弟弟脑子里之外的任何事
That's not a demon sticking needles into my brother's brain.
将就我一下 你怎么样了
Yeah,humor me,how are you doing.
我还好
I'm okay.
很好 不错
Good,good,that's.
所以 你换了电池之后
So,what,you just change your battery.
能量就立刻恢复了 这么容易吗
And your power's back up,it's that easy.
不是那么容易 但是
It wasn't easy,but.
我也没有别的选择
I didn't have a choice.
一般都是这样
That's usually how it goes.
Cass 我很抱歉
Cass,I'm sorry.
抱歉什么
About what.
把你赶出基地
Kicking you out of the bunker.
还有 把Sam的情况一直瞒着你
That's,you know,not telling you about Sam.
你觉得他当时命悬一线
You thought his life was at stake.
是啊 但我被人骗了
Yeah,I got played.
我之前也以为我能拯救天堂
I thought I was saving heaven.
然后我也被骗了
I got played too.
你的意思是我们就是一对蠢货吗
So you say we're both a couple of dumb asses.
我比较喜欢 轻信 这个词
I prefer the word,trusting.
不那么蠢 没那么难听
Less dumb,less ass.
Laverne Shirley 别调情了 快过来
Laverne!Shirley!Get in here.
虽然他晕过去了
Pinhead's out cold.
但你们来看这个
But watch this.
他在说什么
What is he saying.
他的名字
His name.
Gadreel
Gadreel.
你想起什么了吗
That means something to you.
难怪我从来没见过他
Well,that's why I've never seen him.
他从创世以来就一直在监狱里
He's been imprisoned since the dawn of time.
他就是那个
Gadreel was the eccentric.
让Lucifer进入花园的疯子
Who allowed Lucifer into the garden.
哦 哦 还是个名人啊
My,my,a celebrity.
但是 花园
But the garden.
伊甸园吗 亚当和夏娃的花园
Like,Eden,Adam and Eve,fig-leaves garden.
是他的错
It's his fault.
都是他的错
All of it.
人类的堕落
The corruption of man.
恶魔 地狱 上帝的出走就是因为他
Demons,hell,God left because of him.
大天使们 甚至是天启
The archangels,the apocalypse.
如果他不那么软弱的话 这些都不会发生
If he hadn't been so weak,none of it would happen.
你毁了整个宇宙 你这个混蛋
You ruined the universe,you damn son of a bitch.
Cass
Cass.
Dean
Dean.
我理解你
I get it.
但是你得冷静
But you gotta chill.
为什么拖了这么长时间
What's taking so long.
除了因为我正在解开一个
Other than the fact that I'm trying to unravel.
复杂的多维度能量节之外
A living multidimensional knot of pure energy.
还真没什么别的原因了
Not much.
不会成功的
It won't work.
你永远也不会找到你弟弟
You will never find your brother.
尽管激怒我好了
Go ahead,poke and prod.
我可以年复一年地坐在这里看着你们失败
I can sit in this chair for years and watch you fail.
一次又一次地失败
Over and over again.
比这糟糕的情况我都撑下来了 Dean
I've endured much worse than this,Dean.
糟糕得多的
So much worse.
我的时间多着呢
And I have all the time in this world.
闭嘴
Shut up.
好的 B计划
All right,plan B.
Cass
Cass.
你得附他的身
You have to possess him.
什么
What.
现在就行动
Do it now.
你去告诉Sam现在的情况
Get in there,tell Sam what's going on.
然后让他把那个撒谎的混蛋踹出来
And kick that lying son of bitch out.
这也许可以起效
It might work.
但是未经允许我不可以随便附身
But I can't possess a vessel without permission.
不 不行
No,not happening.
别蠢了
Don't be daft.
恶魔可以随心所欲的附身任何人
Demons can take what they want.
我能一铲子挖进这小东西的脑子里
I can burrow into that rat's nest of a head.
还可以叫醒Sam
I can wake Sam up.
我是C计划
Let's call me plan C.
你还有更好的主意吗
You got a better idea.
那个天使怎么办
What about the angel.
我不会待很久的
I won't last.
如果他找到了你
And what if he finds you.
我就逃走
I'll run.
我不会为你赔上性命的
I'm not dying for you.
当然 如果我这么做的话
Of course if I do this.
- 你就得 - 给你解开镣铐 我懂
- You're gonna have to - Take off the leash,I know.
而且你永远不许再拴住我了
And it stays off.
我救了Sam 你们就还我自由之身
I save Sam.I leave here a free man.
成交吗
Do we have a deal.
Cass 烧掉Sam的纹身
Cass,burn off Sam's tattoo.
Dean
Dean.
动手
Do it.
听我的
要是你敢捣乱
If you mess with Sam.
要是你试图不轨
If you try anything.
我会遵守交易的
I keep my bargains.
再说 我根本就不愿意
Besides I don't want to be inside.
待在你弟弟身体里太长时间
Your brother any longer than I have to.
我一秒都不会多待
I'm not one for sloppy seconds.
你找到他的时候
When you find him.
说 波基普西
Say Poughkeepsie.
我们之间的暗语 意思是什么都不要管 快逃
It's our code word means drop everything and run.
好吧
Fine.
我不在的时候
But I'm gone.
别乱动我的肉身
Hands off the suit.
我会弄死你
I will destroy you.
来啊
Eat me.
恶魔和天使同时在我弟弟身体里
A demon and an angel walk into my brother.
听起来好像冷笑话
Sounds like a bad joke.
Dean 如果行不通的话
Dean,if this doesn't work.
行得通
It'll work.
这根本没什么道理啊
I mean It just doesn't make any sense.
为什么这个食尸鬼只吃死掉的拉拉队长
Why is this ghoul chomping on dead cheerleaders.
要啤酒吗
You want a beer.
不用了
No I'm fine.
还不错
Not bad.
Dean Dean
Dean!Dean.
波基普西
Poughkeepsie.
你怎么知道这个词的
How do you know that word.
因为是Dean送我进来的 麋鹿同学
Because Dean sent me Bullwinkle.
真正的Dean 我长话短说
The real Dean ,I'll make this quick.
你被一个天使附身了 他把你关进了一个
You've been possessed by an angel and he's got you.
你自己思维里的小角落
Packed away in some dusty corner of your own mind.
我是来救你出去的
And I'm here to break you out.
认真的吗
Seriously.
好吧
Fine.
那就玩玩儿好了
We'll do this the fun way.
看到了吧
See.
如我所说 都不是真的
Not real,like I said.
我知道附身是什么情况
I know how possession works,Sam.
你能看到所有 他看到的东西
You've seen everything that he's seen.
即使你不记得了
Even if you can't remember.
所以我需要你做的是
So what I need you to do.
把记忆找回来
I need you to remember.
我杀了Kevin吗
Did I kill Kevin.
不是你杀的 是他
No,you didn't,he did.
你要掌控你自己 Sam
You need to take control Sam.
掌控一切
Blow it up.
把那个混蛋天使赶出去
And cast that punk ass holy roller out.
怎么了
What.
真讨厌
Oh bollocks.
你好 Sam
Hello Sam.
你是谁
Who are you.
他名字叫Gadreel
His name is Gadreel.
最早的那个笨蛋
The original chump.
曾经是
Was a chump.
但是现在
And now.
我要带领
I'm going to be the one.
我的族人回天堂
That leads my kind back to heaven.
我将是一个英雄
I'm going to be a hero.
而你 恶魔
But you,demon.
从始至终就只能是一个懦夫
For all your chatter you will always be a coward.
你应该逃跑了
You should be running.
放弃吧 小朋友 你还不够壮
Give up boy,you are not strong enough.
自己控制自己Sam
Take control Sam.
把他赶出去
Cast him out.
你给我出
Get out of my.
你确定你想让我走吗
Are you sure you want me to go.
或许我才是那个让你不散架的关键
Maybe I'm the only thing holding you together.
我走了你会死
I leave you might die.
我说了
I said.
滚
Get.
出
The hell.
去
Out.
在等什么人吗
Waiting for someone.
是的
I am.
不过他迟到了
And he's late.
我愿意
Yes.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
Winchester兄弟找你麻烦了
Winchester trouble.
Sam
Sam.
Cass
Cass.
我很好 多谢关心
I'm fine thanks for asking.
Sam 你没事吧
Sam,are you OK.
Cass
Cass.
是Abaddon
It's Abaddon.
走
Go.
走后门
The back door.
我来应付
I'll handle this.
因为你是个大好人吗
Oh cause you're such a good guy.
眼下我是你这辈子遇到过的最好的人
Right now I'm the goodest guy you've ever got.
这不代表我们俩两清了
This don't make us square.
我还会找你的
I see you again.
我是你的 我明白 我也爱你
I'm dead,Yes I know,I love you too.
跟你们一起工作真是荣幸之至啊
Pleasure doing business with you boys as always.
你好啊 亲爱的
Hello darling.
Crowley
Crowley.
把他的人头给我拿下
Bring me his head.
看到了吗 这就是恶魔
See that's the thing about demons.
他们的服从只是暂时的
They are only obedient to a point.
好吧 让我们谈谈
Right,let's have a chat.
我不是来聊天的
I'm not here to talk.
我也没跟你说话
And I'm not talking to you.
我在跟他们说 其他的恶魔们
I'm talking to them,the average demons.
因为我能感受到他们的痛苦
Because I feel their pains.
你们一定过得很艰辛
You must have been difficult.
你们的王被从你们身边带走
With your loving king so cruely be taken from ya.
我想你们一定觉得茫然不知所措
I imagine you felt all at sea.
随之而来的是
And then along came.
一个小畜生
The brute.
她很强壮
She's strong.
挂着骑士的头衔 有着永生的能力
And a knight and immortal at the moment.
所以看见一些愚笨的旧部下买了她的账
So I'm not surprised that some of my.
我并不惊讶
More idiotic subject bought her line.
但是现在 好消息 同志们
But now,good news fellas.
老爸回家了
Daddy's home.
地狱不欢迎你 Crowley
Hell doesn't want you Crowley.
它是我的
It's mine.
是吗
Is it.
我在这儿就不是
Not would I here.
我还活着一天就不是
Not while I'm still kicking.
好吧那就让我们解决这个问题
Well let's settle it.
你和我此时此地
You and me right here.
成者为王败者为寇
Winner takes the ground.
看
See.
这就是你的问题了 亲爱的
That's your problem love.
你认为这是场战争
You think that is a fight.
不是吗
It's not.
这是一场竞赛
It's a campaign.
人心和头脑才是最重要的
Hearts and minds that's what's important.
恶魔们可以做出选择
See demons have a choice.
他们可以选择屈从这个暴怒的红发女人
Take orders from the world angriest ginger.
没有权利 没有尊严
And that's saying something.
或者加入我的团队
Or join my team.
我保证所有人都有发言权 一个处女
Where everyone gets a say,a virgin.
还有一大堆鲜美的内脏
And all the entrails they can eat.
好好想想吧 伙计们
So think on this lads.
给大家传话
Spread the word.
支持Crowley
Vote Crowley.
觉得好点了吗
You feel better.
好点了
A little yeah.
要完全治愈你还需要时间
It'll take time to fully heal you.
必须一步一步来
We have to do it in stages.
好了 有什么话就说吧
All right let me hear it.
你想让我说什么 我生气了
What you want me to say,I'm pissed.
好吧是的 我生气了
OK I am,I'm pissed.
你骗我 又一次
You lie to me,again.
我没得选
I didn't have a choice.
我已经准备好去死了 Dean
I was ready to die,Dean.
我知道
I know.
但是我没让你这么做
But I wouldn't let you.
因为那不是我
Because it's not in me.
所以呢 你就决定骗我
So what,you decide to trick me.
让我被一个神经天使附身
Into being possessed by some psycho angel.
他救了你的命
He saved your life.
那又如何
So what.
我愿意去死
I was willing to die.
现在呢
And now.
Kevin
Kevin.
不 这事儿不能怪你
No,that is not on you.
Kevin的血染在我手上
Kevin's blood is on my hands.
我永远也洗不清
And that ain't never getting clean.
我会为此下地狱的
I'll burn for that.
我会的
I will.
但是我会找到Gadreel
But I will find Gadreel.
我会杀了那个混蛋
And I will end that son of a bitch.
但是我会一个人去
But I'll do it alone.
什么意思
What's that suppose to mean.
拜托
Come on man.
你不明白吗
Can't you see.
我被诅咒了
I'm poisoned.
Sam 靠近我的人
Sam people that get close to me.
都会死
They get killed.
或者更糟
Or worse.
是 我告诉自己我救的人比我伤的人更多
Yeah I tell myself that I helped more people than I hurt.
我告诉我自己我做这些是出于好意
And I tell myself that I do it all for the right reasons.
我也相信是这样
And I believe that.
但是我不能 也不会
But I can't,I won't.
再让别人跟我一起趟这浑水
Drag anybody to the muck with me.
再也不能了
Not anymore.
走吧
Go.
我不会拦着你的
I'm not gonna stop you.
但别觉得这是一切的症结所在 因为事实并不是这样
But don't go thinking that's the problem cause it's not.
什么意思
What's that suppose to mean.
你走吧
Just go